<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<JournalEntries>
	<Person>
		<Entry date="01/01/01">
			<Paragraph1>I’m scared.  Today, dad called me into his room.  He said that this plague wasn’t normal.  He gave me a pile of papers and said that they were entrusted to him by a close friend - the family doctor who used to take care of my sisters and I back when we were kids.  Then he started crying and shaking, sputtering incoherently about how my sisters didn’t have to die, how children are so rare these days as it is, and something about how the plague shouldn’t have happened.  Are these papers somehow about the sickness?  Some of these pages looked like they’re falling apart they’re so old.  What does he want me to do?  I’m going to read these papers as soon as I get off work.  </Paragraph1>
			<Paragraph2>This is impossible.  This first entry must me two thousand years old, at least.  But the college of medicine claims to be as old as the city, so this crazy story checks out.  But dad must have believed it, or he wouldn’t have - oh god, Doctor Samson!  He must have been…  This is…  I’m going to finish this.  I’m going to find my way into the medical school’s records and I’m going to finish translating this tablet of theirs.  I don’t know what’s going on, but Doctor Samson believed that translating the tablet would make things clear.  And, if he’s to be believed, they are also responsible for the secret murders of at least three people.  Of course, if he’s to be believed…  then he’s responsible for many more.  </Paragraph2>
		</Entry>
		<Entry date="01/01/05">
			<Paragraph1>The sunrise was so beautiful.  Funny how these things work - it was the most horrifying day of my life.  I can’t believe it….  They killed all those people.  He said that they do this every time the population gets too high - how many times have they done this?  How many dead children because of these monsters?  Samson said that they couldn’t control it….  I’m going to tell everyone about the red flowers.  Most of them are gone, but you still see one or two in the old part of town.  But even that might be too late.  There are so few of us left.  Among those, how many can even still have children?  This might be the end.  I pray that it won’t be.  </Paragraph1>
			<Paragraph2></Paragraph2>
		</Entry>
	</Person>
</JournalEntries>